<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-15"?>
<COLLECTION>
<DOCTRAIN>
<TOPIC> <D>18</D> </TOPIC>
<TITLE>
Debian project
</TITLE>
<BODY>
In rolling, trunk rotation and elbow support were difficult for the
most severely diplegic children. In 2 patients, carotid angiography
demonstrated segmental narrowing and occlusion of the middle cerebral
artery. Part I of this paper describes some of the pathophysiological
events leading to ischaemic brain injury. Cardiac autonomic function
was measured in 25 subjects with insulin-dependent diabetes mellitus
and 11 control subjects. Molecular analysis of this abnormality
demonstrated a deletion within the fifth intron of the c-sis gene. Men
who reported pain in the preceding year were more likely to use
multiple analgesic products. We present our experience in the surgical
management of 25 consecutive patients treated for these problems. We
conclude that topographic mapping is a valid technique in the
detection of localized cerebral lesions. The highest incidence of
remote neuromuscular disorders in cancer has previously been reported
in lung carcinoma. Blacks and Japanese have more intracranial
occlusive cerebrovascular disease, while whites have more
extracranial disease. Forty-six percent of the patients had a more or
less pronounced tilt of the pituitary stalk. Adult male Sprague-Dawley
rats underwent spinal cord trauma at the midthoracic level using a
weight-dropping technique. We present the case of an 18-year-old woman
with intractable complex partial seizures since age 13. A 64-year-old
man presented with the acute onset of unilateral blindness and
ipsilateral ocular motor paresis. Two patients had had ischemic
strokes 5 months and 18 years, respectively, before transplantation. A
qualitative assessment of edema was made from light and electron
micrographs of the cerebral cortex. A case is presented of a child
with trauma to the vertebrobasilar artery resulting in stroke. uring
the 10-minute apnea tests, nine patients were given continuous apneic
oxygenation by tracheal cannula.
</BODY>
</DOCTRAIN>
</COLLECTION>
