<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-15"?>
<COLLECTION>
<DOCTRAIN>
<TOPIC> <D>18</D> </TOPIC>
<TITLE> Test </TITLE>
<BODY>
Since the patient was scheduled for extensive surgery in the prone
position, it was decided to use transoesophageal pacing as the method
of choice for conversion of SVT. Gamma camera imaging of the head,
neck, and upper thorax was undertaken, in the lateral projection, during 
the swallowing of the radiolabeled bolus of water. To find a simple
and reliable means to measure vibration sensations, 189 diabetic
patients and 88 control subjects were tested at different sites with a
graduated tuning fork. With few exceptions, use of multiple analgesic
drugs achieves dubious increases in analgesia while placing elders at
increased risk of the many potential adverse effects of analgesic
drugs. With few exceptions, use of multiple analgesic drugs achieves
dubious increases in analgesia while placing elders at increased risk
of the many potential adverse effects of analgesic drugs. Magnetic
resonance imaging gave useful information about the site of the
lesions responsible for the presenting syndrome and provided
additional information in support of a diagnosis of multiple
sclerosis. Whereas CT was unable to distinguish mass lesions caused by
toxoplasmosis from those caused by lymphoma, 71 % of the solitary
lesions seen on MR images were lymphomas. Clinical follow-up for a
mean interval of 28 months on 20 of the 22 symptomatic patients not
undergoing surgery revealed no strokes and transient recurrent
symptoms in two patients. 69 other children were admitted with
clinical features strongly suggestive of cerebral malaria but with
negative blood films; 16 of these died and 3 had re
sidual neurological deficits. This hypothesis suggests that
antioxidant therapies may slow the rate of progression of PD and
raises concern that metabolites of levodopa therapy may accelerate the
rate of neuronal degeneration. Diagnosis of congenital toxoplasmosis
was based on a positive toxoplasma culture of amniotic fluid or fetal
blood and on the presence of specific immunoglobulin M antibodies in
fetal blood. The highest densities of hybridization were distributed
within hippocampal pyramidal and granule cells, medial habenula,
Purkinje cells and the molecular layer of cerebellum, and olfactory
bulb. We believe this to be the first case of temporal lobe
encephalocele and epilepsy to be diagnosed preoperatively, and the
first case also to be associated with meningoangiomatosis. The
cumulative incidence of ischemic stroke was significantly less in the
patients with Parkinson's disease than in the controls, as was the
cumulative incidence of myocardial infarction. These findings suggest
hemodynamic vulnerability of the watershed areas after internal
carotid artery occlusion in persons with good collateral circulation
through the anterior portion of the circle of Willis. Next, the
anterior clinoid process and the optic nerve are involved, and,
finally, thrombosis of the aneurysmal cavity extends into the
internal carotid artery itself. We conclude that the risk of an acute
neurologic insult with orthotopic cardiac transplantation is low but
may result from drug toxicity, cerebral ischemia, or hemorrhagic
mechanisms. Therapy emphasized instruction in motor planning, balance
and weight shift, and the use of adaptive equipment; these motor
abilities were then practiced within real life situations. Manual
stretch treatment, properly applied to extrinsic finger flexor
muscles, is an effective method of temporarily improving the control
of finger extension movement in spastic hemiparetic subjects.
</BODY>
</DOCTRAIN>
</COLLECTION>
